(Raj:)And here's your daddy.
(Raj:)When he tries to tell
you he used to be cool,
(Raj:)you can see he wasn't.
(Raj:)All right,
enough with the camera.
(Raj:)Well, this is not for me.
This is for the baby.
(Raj:)Some day she's gonna
want to see this.
(Bernadette:)I'm sorry.
Who's gonna want to see this?
I... I said “she,”
but lots of things are she--
(Raj:)boats
(Raj:)and cars,
(Raj:)whales.
Like, “Thar she blows.”
(Stuart:)You're doing great.
Raj!
(Raj:)Well, okay,
I'm gonna sign off now.
(Raj:)This next part may contain
some adult language.
How could you?!
(Howard:)We made it this
far without knowing,
and you ruined it!
(Raj:)Well, you guys have no idea
how hard it is
(Raj:)to know something like this
and not say it!
(Stuart:)You told me it was a girl,
and I didn't say it.
Raj!
You were supposed
(Raj:)to keep that to yourself.